What was the biggest lesson that you learned from playing football that you kind
of used to help adapt into the business owner and leader that you are today?
First, you learn how to work with a
team. You learn how to deal with adversity.
But I would say those are all
the common things that you see in sports.
But I would say the best thing that
I learned actually came from my mistakes in sports.
So I played quarterback. I
was a scrappy dual threat quarterback.
And when I was at Long Beach City College, a junior college
just outside of Los Angeles, I had these two coaches that were fantastic.
I'm still talking to you. Brad
Peabody and Ryan Flynn. Unbelievable coaches.
But the problem was, is I was
obsessed with trying to do everything my way.
I thought, I didn't think I just knew more than them, but they would
teach it to me and I was just always trying to do it my way.
I didn't stick to the basics. And I worked very, very, very
hard, but I never fully used my brain like I could have.